Kaufman, Jacob J. Papers 6190
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Publications on Education, Employment, and General Labor Issues. (Box 1)
  - The Research Potential Related to Law Enforcement and the Administration of Justice, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: The Research Potential Related to Law Enforcement and the Administration of Justice, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
      Notes: July 1968.
    - Item 2: The Research Potential Related to Law Enforcement and the Administration of Justice, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
      Notes: July 1968. Copy 2.
  - The Role of Labor in Community Action Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: The Role of Labor in Community Action Programs, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
      Notes: Paper presented to the Central Pennsylvania Conference on "Appalachia and the Economic Opportunity Act", April 21, 1975.
  - Speaking Freely: Theodore Kheel, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Speaking Freely: Theodore Kheel, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
      Author: Theodore Kheel; Edwin Newman
      Notes: Interview of Theodore Kheel
  - Strikes and Collective Bargaining, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Strikes and Collective Bargaining, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
      Author: Alice Beamsderfer
      Notes: January 1975.
  - Book Reviews by Jacob Kaufman, 1949-1967 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Publications on Railroads., Publication (Box 2)
  - An Analysis of the Work of the President's Railroad Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: An Analysis of the Work of the President's Railroad Commission, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Magazine, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
      Notes: v.150:no.3 (1961:Mar.)
  - Collective Bargaining and Grievance Procedures in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining and Grievance Procedures in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Grievance Procedures in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Communicator, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: The Communicator, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Author: Conrail
      Notes: News and Views of the Altoona Shops, Issue no.1
  - Conrail Labor-Management Project, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Summary Annual Report, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Author: Conrail Labor- Management Project
      Notes: August 1, 1985. Projected Year Ended June 30, 1985.
    - Item 2: Quarterly Progress Report, 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Notes: April-June 1986.
  - Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Author: Federal Railroad Administration
      Notes: FRA Docket no.RSOR-6, Notice no.4
    - Item 2: Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Notes: FRA Docket no.RSOR-6, Notice no.4. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Notes: FRA Docket no.RSOR-6, Notice no.4. Copy 3.
  - Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Control of Alcohol and Drug Use in Railroad Operations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Notes: Field Manual
  - Due Process on the Railroads, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Due Process on the Railroads, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Author: Joseph Lazar
  - Economics of Minimum Wages in Relation to the Agriculturea Labor Market, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Economics of Minimum Wages in Relation to the Agriculturea Labor Market, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Notes: Reprinted from the Journal of Farm Economics, v.31:no.4 (1949:Nov.).
    - Item 2: Economics of Minimum Wages in Relation to the Agriculturea Labor Market, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Notes: Reprinted from the Journal of Farm Economics, v.31:no.4 (1949:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Emergency Board no.198, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Emergency Board no.198, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Author: Emergency Board no.198
      Notes: December 17, 1982.
  - Emergency Boards Under the Railway Labor Act, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Emergency Boards Under the Railway Labor Act, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Notes: Published in Labor Law Journal, v.9:no.12 (1958:Dec.)
    - Item 2: Emergency Boards Under the Railway Labor Act, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, v.9:no.12 (1958:Dec.). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Emergency Boards Under the Railway Labor Act, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, v.9:no.12 (1958:Dec.). Copy 3.
  - Evolution of Work Rules in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Evolution of Work Rules in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Evolution of Work Rules in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Featherbedding on the Railroads: By Law and By Agreement, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Featherbedding on the Railroads: By Law and By Agreement, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Author: J. A. Lipowski
      Notes: v.8 (1967).
  - Free Collective Bargaining vs. Compulsory Arbitration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Free Collective Bargaining vs. Compulsory Arbitration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Author: Switchmen's Union of North America (SUNA)
  - Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Notes: Reprinted from Current Economic Comment, v.20:no.3 (1958:Aug.)
    - Item 2: Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Notes: Typed manuscript for article in Current Economic Comment, v.20:no.3 (1958:Aug.)
  - Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Author: Michael Cimini
      Notes: December 1971.
    - Item 2: Government Intervention in Railroad Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Notes: December 1971. Copy 2.
  - Grievance Arbitration in the Railroad Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Grievance Arbitration in the Railroad Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, March 1958.
    - Item 2: Grievance Arbitration in the Railroad Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, March 1958. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Grievance Arbitration in the Railroad Industry, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, March 1958. Copy 3.
  - Grievance Procedure at the Local Level, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Grievance Procedure at the Local Level, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
    - Item 2: Grievance Procedure at the Local Level, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Notes: Photocopy. Copy 2.
  - Grievance Procedures Under the Railway Labor Act, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Grievance Procedures Under the Railway Labor Act, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Notes: Reprinted from the Southern Economic Journal, v.19:No.1 (1952:July)
  - Handling Rail Disputes Under the Railway Labor Act, 1950-1969, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Handling Rail Disputes Under the Railway Labor Act, 1950-1969, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Author: Bureau of Labor Statistics
      Notes: Bulletin 1753
  - The Impact of Railroad Mergers and Consolidations on Labor, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: The Impact of Railroad Mergers and Consolidations on Labor, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Matthew A. Kelly
      Notes: July 15, 1977.
    - Item 2: The Impact of Railroad Mergers and Consolidations on Labor, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Notes: July 15, 1977. Copy 2.
  - Jack Haley and His Chicago Central Crew, 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Jack Haley and His Chicago Central Crew, 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Author: Philip R. Hastings
      Notes: August 1986.
  - Keep It Moving: Buffalo Terminal Project, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Keep It Moving: Buffalo Terminal Project, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Notes: July 1980. Labor/Management Task Force
  - Labor Disputes in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Labor Disputes in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: Labor Disputes in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Likely Issues in Collective Bargaining, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Likely Issues in Collective Bargaining, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Notes: Centennial Issue (1957:Sep.)
  - Logic and Meaning of Work Rules on the Railroads, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Logic and Meaning of Work Rules on the Railroads, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Notes: Reprinted from Proceedings of the Fourteenth Annual Meeting of the Industrial Relations Research Association, December 28-29, 1961.
    - Item 2: Logic and Meaning of Work Rules on the Railroads, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Notes: Reprinted from Proceedings of the Fourteenth Annual Meeting of the Industrial Relations Research Association, December 28-29, 1961. copy 2.
  - The National Mediation Board at Fifty, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: The National Mediation Board at Fifty, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Author: Charles M. Rehmus
      Notes: December 1984.
  - Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force: Final Report, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force: Final Report, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Author: Ohio High Speed Rail Task Force
      Notes: June 1985.
  - Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    v.86 (1961:Sep. 27). Copy 1
    - Item 1: Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Notes: v.86 (1961:Sep. 27). Copy 1
  - Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    v.86 (1961:Sep. 27). Copy 2
    - Item 1: Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
      Notes: v.86 (1961:Sep. 27). Copy 2
  - Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    v.87 (1961:Sep. 28). Copy 1
    - Item 1: Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Notes: v.87 (1961:Sep. 28). Copy 1
  - Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    v.87 (1961:Sep. 28). Copy 2
    - Item 1: Presidential Railroad Commission. Transcript of Proceedings, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
      Notes: v.87 (1961:Sep. 28). Copy 2
  - Procedures Versus Collective Bargaining in Railroad Labor Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Procedures Versus Collective Bargaining in Railroad Labor Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.25:no.1 (1971:Oct.)
    - Item 2: Procedures Versus Collective Bargaining in Railroad Labor Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.25:no.1 (1971:Oct.). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Procedures Versus Collective Bargaining in Railroad Labor Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.25:no.1 (1971:Oct.). Copy 3.
  - A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 Progress Report, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: A Program of Experiments Involving Changes in Terminal Operations, 1974 Progress Report, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
      Author: Labor/Management Task Force on Terminals
  - Progress Report of the Milwaukee Road's Labor-Management Action Group, 1983; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Progress Report of the Milwaukee Road's Labor-Management Action Group, 1983; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Author: Labor-Management Action Group
  - Project REAP, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Project REAP, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Author: Railroad Personnel Association
  - Proposal for Expanding Economic Development in New York State Through Effective Use of Rail System, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Proposal for Expanding Economic Development in New York State Through Effective Use of Rail System, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Author: Robert J. Pasciullo
      Notes: December 13, 1985.
    - Item 2: Proposal for Expanding Economic Development in New York State Through Effective Use of Rail System, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Notes: December 11, 1985. Draft
  - Rail Merger Study, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Rail Merger Study: Role of Government, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Author: Rail Services Planning Office
      Notes: Issue Paper no.5 (1977:Aug. 1)
    - Item 2: Rail Merger Study: Alternatives to Merger, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Notes: Issue Paper no.7 (1977:Aug. 18)
    - Item 3: Rail Merger Study: Final Report, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
      Notes: Final Report (1978:Feb. 1)
  - Railroad Employment in New York and New Jersey, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Railroad Employment in New York and New Jersey, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - The Railroad Labor Dispute: A Marathon of Maneuver and Improvisation, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: The Railroad Labor Dispute: A Marathon of Maneuver and Improvisation, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.18:no.2 (1965:Jan.)
    - Item 2: The Railroad Labor Dispute: A Marathon of Maneuver and Improvisation, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.18:no.2 (1965:Jan.). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: The Railroad Labor Dispute: A Marathon of Maneuver and Improvisation, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.18:no.2 (1965:Jan.). Copy 3.
  - The Railway Labor Act, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: The Railway Labor Act, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Notes: Title 45: United States Code, Chapter 8, Sections 151-188. 1982 Edition
  - The Railway Labor Act in Action, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: The Railway Labor Act in Action, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Item 2: The Railway Labor Act in Action, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Item 3: The Railway Labor Act in Action, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Notes: Copy 3.
  - Railway. Summary Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Copy 1.
    - Item 1: Railway. Productivity Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
      Author: Railway Industry Study Team
      Notes: Copy 1.
      Language: Japanese.
    - Item 2: Railway. Productivity Summary Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Railway. Summary Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Copy 2.
    - Item 1: Railway. Productivity Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Item 2: Railway. Productivity Summary Report no.34, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Representation in the Railroad Industry, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Representation in the Railroad Industry, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 46)
      Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, July 1955.
  - The Scarborough and Whitby Railway, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: The Scarborough and Whitby Railway, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 47)
      Author: J. Robin Lidster
      Notes: A Photographic and Historical Survey
  - Statement fo Neil P. Speirs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Statement fo Neil P. Speirs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 48)
      Author: Neil P. Speirs
  - TWU Calendar, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: TWU Calendar, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 49)
      Author: Transport Workers Union of America
  - Tracking Facts, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Tracking Facts, 1985; Publication (Box 2, Folder 50)
      Notes: v.1:no.3 (1985:July)
- Publications on Railroads and Kaufman's ILR Courses and Research., Publication (Box 3)
  - UTU Background, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: UTU Background: a Report from Headquarters, 1983; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Author: United Transportation Union (UTU)
      Notes: v.14:no.1 (1983:Jan./Feb.)
    - Item 2: UTU Background: a Report from Headquarters, 1983; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.14:no.4 (1983:July/Aug.)
  - UTU Directory, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: UTU Directory: International Headquarters and Locals, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Notes: June 1986.
  - UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.5 (1986:May)
    - Item 2: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.6 (1986:June)
    - Item 3: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.6 (1986:June). Copy 2.
    - Item 4: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.7 (1986:July)
    - Item 5: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.7 (1986:July). Copy 2.
    - Item 6: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.8 (1986:Aug.)
    - Item 7: UTU News, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.18:no.11 (1986:Nov.)
  - UTU Pamphlets, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Alcohol: Sensible Drinker, Problem Drinker, Alcoholic, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 2: People Helping People, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: PR Series no.9. What every UTU Member should know about Employee Assistance Programs.
    - Item 3: What 100 Railroad Jobs Mean to Communities Across the United States, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 4: What 100 Railroad Jobs Mean to Communities Across the United States, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 5: I've Looked Away Too Long, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: Operation RedBlock poster
    - Item 6: If You Have a Problem With Drink or Drugs You Are Not Alone, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 7: Help Stop Alcohol and Drug Abuse: Support Your Employee Assistance Program, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: Poster
    - Item 8: Help Stop Alcohol and Drug Abuse: Support Your Employee Assistance Program, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: Poster. Copy 2.
    - Item 9: Your Labor Union, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 10: Reporter: A UTU "A" Card is Your Passport to a Union of Your Choice on Amtrak, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Author: United Transportation Union (UTU); Cliff Merritt
    - Item 11: Reporter: A UTU "A" Card is Your Passport to a Union of Your Choice on Amtrak, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 12: Reporter: A UTU "A" Card is Your Passport to a Union of Your Choice on Amtrak, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 13: Reporter: Who Says You Don't Have a Right to a Union of Your Own Choosing?, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 14: Reporter: Who Says You Don't Have a Right to a Union of Your Own Choosing?, 1984; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Union Pacific Railway Employee Assistance Program Activitiy Report, 1972-1985, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Union Pacific Railway Employee Assistance Program Activitiy Report, 1972-1985, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Author: Union Pacific Railroad
  - Wage Criteria in the Railroad Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Wage Criteria in the Railroad Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Author: Jacob J. Kaufman; Frederic Meyers
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.6:no.1 (1952:Oct.)
    - Item 2: Wage Criteria in the Railroad Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.6:no.1 (1952:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - The Wage-Price Relationship in the Railroad Industry: A Comment, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: The Wage-Price Relationship in the Railroad Industry: A Comment, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: Reprinted from the Journal of Business of the University of Chicago, v.26:no.1 (1953:Jan.)
    - Item 2: The Wage-Price Relationship in the Railroad Industry: A Comment, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: Reprinted from the Journal of Business of the University of Chicago, v.26:no.1 (1953:Jan.). Copy 2.
  - Work Rule Problems With Particular Reference to the Railroad Industry: Myths and Realities, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Work Rule Problems With Particular Reference to the Railroad Industry: Myths and Realities, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 2: Work Rule Problems With Particular Reference to the Railroad Industry: Myths and Realities, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: Supplementay paper for the 1st World Congress of the International Industrial Relations Association, September 4-8, 1967. Researched under a Ford Foundation Faculty Research Fellowship in 1962-1963. Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Work Rule Problems With Particular Reference to the Railroad Industry: Myths and Realities, 1967; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: Supplementay paper for the 1st World Congress of the International Industrial Relations Association, September 4-8, 1967. Researched under a Ford Foundation Faculty Research Fellowship in 1962-1963. Copy 3.
  - Work Rules and Labor-Management Relations in the Railroad Industy, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Work Rules and Labor-Management Relations in the Railroad Industy, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: May 23, 1973.
  - Working Rules in the Railroad Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Working Rules in the Railroad Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: Published in Labor Law Journal, v.5:no.12 (1954:Dec.)
    - Item 2: Working Rules in the Railroad Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: Published in Labor Law Journal, v.5:no.12 (1954:Dec.). Photocopy. Copy 2.